Guide to the Rice University Committee on Undergraduate Teaching, 1967-1984 UA 176
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Committee on Undergraduate Teaching records
1967-1984
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 176
0.5 Linear Feet (1 box)
The memoranda, reports, proposals and correspondence generated by or for the Rice University Committee on Undergraduate Teaching.
Biographical / Historical
The Rice University Committee on Undergraduate Teaching's charge is to "promote excellence in undergraduate teaching by assisting with the evaluation of teaching, by providing support to faculty for participation in appropriate courses and seminars, and by providing funds for new instructional methods and programs". (Committee announcement, February 1972)
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the memoranda, reports, proposals and correspondence generated by or for the Committee on Undergraduate Teaching. The collection is arranged chronologically and does not include the questionnaire forms of student evaluations.
Access Restrictions
Permission to use papers must be obtained from the President's Office, Rice University. Contact woodson@rice.edu for assistance. Stored off-site at the Library Service Center.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
President's Papers (Hackerman); Provost's Papers
Index Terms
Subjects
Faculty; Universities and colleges
Document Types
memorandums; letters (correspondence)
Places
Rice University
- Series I: Memos, correspondence and reports, 166306
  - Memos and correspondence, 1967-68; 150209 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Memos and reports, 1970-71; 150210 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Memos, letters of appointment, and correspondence, 1971-72; 150211 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Memos, reports, and correspondence, 1972-73; 150212 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Memos, reports, and appointment letters, 1973-74; 150213 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Memos, reports, and appointment letters, 1974-75; 150214 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Memos, reports, and appointments letters, 1975-76; 150215 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Memos, proposals, and appointment letters, 1976-77; 150216 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Memos, proposals, reports, and appointment letter, 1977-78; 150217 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Memos, proposals, and appointment letters, 1978-79; 150218 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Memos and correspondence, 1979-80; 150219 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Memos, 1980-84; 150220 (Box 1, Folder 12)